Finding Aid for the Centennial History Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Centennial History
multiple
University Archives
RG.0101
1 linear_feet
- Entrance Records - Examination Record (Volume 3), 1894-1903 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Entrance Records - Examination Record (Volume 4), 1904-1909 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Grade Book, 1895-1897 (Volume 11) (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Grade Book, 1900-1902 (Volume 14) (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Grade Book, 1900 (Volume 17), 1900-1900 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Grade Book, 1902 (Volume 18), 1902-1902 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Grade Book, 1905 (Volume 21), 1905-1905 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Entrance Records - Examination Record (Volume 5), 1909-1909 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Entrance Records - Examination Record (Volume 6), 1923-1945 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Grade Book, 1898 (Volume 12), 1898-1898 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Grade Book, 1899 (Volume 13), 1899-1899 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Grade Book, 1903 (Volume 19), 1903-1903 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Grade Book, 1904-1906 (Volume 20) (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Pharmacy Grade Book, 1895-1902 (Volume 22) (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Pharmacy Grade Book, 1903-1916 (Volume 23) (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Pharmacy Grade Book, 1917-1920 (Volume 24) (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Record of Courses, 1893-1916 (Volume 7), 1983-1916 (Box F-0001, Folder 1)
- Grade Book, 1902-1908 (Volume 15) (Box F-0001, Folder 2)
- Matriculation Book, 1875-1910 (Volume 1), 1897-1910 (Box F-0002, Folder 1)
- Grade Book, 1908-1912 (Volume 16) (Box F-0002, Folder 2)
- Matriculation Book, 1910-1923 (Volume 2) (Box F-0003, Folder 1)
- Grade Book, 1875-1881 (Volume 8) (Box F-0003, Folder 2)
- Grade Book, 1881-1888 (Volume 9) (Box F-0004, Folder 1)
- Grade Book, 1888-1895 (Volume 10) (Box F-0004, Folder 2)